-==本影片由 Y4DG制作团队 荣誉出品==-
更多精彩影视 请访问 http://www.y4dg.com
影片压制: 古来北 字幕翻译：Monsoons 校对：wxysun
字幕组招募QQ号: 605441439
有人说
They say
在临死前的一霎那
that a split second before you die
你的一生 会在眼前一一闪现
your whole life passes before your eyes.
如果一颗子弹从说这话的蠢货眼前擦过
If the moron who said that had a bullet inches from his face
我怀疑他还会不会这么说
I wonder what he'd say.
我两岁的时候
That's me when I was two.
那是我唯一一次对我母亲开枪
It's the only thinp I've pot of my mother.
这张照片
This photo.
她说她在那条街边把我生下来
She said she pave birth to me in the street.
如今看来 我这一生都在这些街道上沦陷了
Now I see I've been trapped in these streets all my life
而且 不出意外的话
and if nothinp chanpes
我永远也摆脱不了这里了
I'll never pet out of here.
霓虹肉身
NE0N FLESH
让我们从头说起
But let's start at the beginning.
生于街边（窑子里）的人都知道 世界上有两种人
Anyone born on the streets knows the world is split in two.
卖家和买家
Those who buy and those who sell.
妓女
Those who supply the flesh
和嫖客
and those who fuck it.
你会是其中之一
You're on one side or the other.
要一条金链子吗
Want a gold chain?
是的 我要了
0K, I'll keep it.
里基 我们得谈谈
Ricky, we have to talk.
我病了
I'm sick.
妈的 普利西斯 太快了
Fuck it, Princess, it's too early.
我得了焦虑症
I'm suffering from anxiety.
我看了精神科医生
I saw the psychiatrist.
他说我身心失调
He says I'm psychosomatic.
公主（普林西斯）脑子不正常
Princess has a screw loose.
她以为国王是她父亲
She thinks the king is her father.
所以她要带着一顶蓝色的假发
That's why she wears a blue wip,
跟她的血液一样的颜色
the same color as her blood.
在她心情好的时候 你可以问问她真实的名字
If she's in a pood mood, you can ask about her real name.
我的名字?
My name?
胡安 卡洛斯
Juan Carlos.
像我父亲
Like my father.
里基，你知道吗 实际上我是一名演员和歌手
Ricky, you know that really I'm an actress and a singer,
艺人在这个国家 要么陪吃要么陪睡
and artists in this country either serve tables or suck dicks.
有一天 我跟一个家伙上了床
The other day I was sucking a guy off.
结果他是一名导演
It turns out he's a director
他正在拍一部片子
and he's making a movie.
片名叫什么
What's it called?
"口交的女仆" 那算是电影吗?
"Maid to Suck". Is that cinema?
嗯...与其说是电影不如说是家庭电影
Well, it's cinema, more like "home cinema",
嗯...也算是电影
but, yeah, it's cinema.
真正的电影
Real cinema.
当初我离开家乡的时候 可没想到会走到这步田地
It's not what I imagined when I left the village,
但我妥协了
but one has to compromise.
停 停
Stop, stop.
你听说过格莱墨 马夫吗?
Do you know Glamour Muff?
她没听说过格莱墨 马夫
She doesn't know Glamour Muff.
当我在"纽约集体性交"发现她时
When I discovered her in "Gang Bangs of New York".
她像你一样忸捏
Chichi was like you,
一名新星正在形成
a star in the making.
我们得专心一点
We had to make the chop.
等等 等等
Wait, wait.
我这样猜对吗
Have I got this right?
只要你同意潜规则
They offered you the lead in a porn movie
他们就让你演黄片的主角
if you cut off your dick.
听上去有点下流
That makes it sound a bit gross,
不过他称之为反美学
but he says it's anti-aesthetic.
我能说什么
What can I say?
我不知道
I don't know.
你聪明 又善解人意
You're intelligent and sensitive.
破处以后 我就再也不善解人意了
Since I had my nipples pierced I'm not sensitive anywhere.
我想着: "脱掉它"
I think: "Cut it off."
"你再也用不着它了"
"You don't use it anyway."
但是正因为这样 才让那些异装癖者看上去有些特别
But it's what makes transvestites a bit special,
我可以用它来挣房租
it pays the rent.
如果我学会潜规则
But if I cut off my dick
我就可以成为电影明星
I could be a movie star.
满世界都是电影 奥斯卡 红毯
The world of movies, 0scars, red carpets...
我下不了决心
I can't decide.
你是怎么陷入这一团糟的?
How do you get into these messes?
不知道
I don't know.
进去继续
Go on inside.
耶稣基督
Jesus Christ.
艾杜 请给我来杯薄荷茶
Edu, may I have a mint tea, please?
你好 安吉利特
Hey, Angelito.
里基 过来坐
Ricky! Come over here.
陪我喝杯咖啡
Have a coffee with me.
来这儿
Here.
怎么了?我不能跟老朋友喝杯咖啡吗
What's up? Can't I have a coffee with a pal?
斯克蕾格效劳于安吉利特
Scrag worked for Angelito.
人们说吸食海洛因 却生就了伟大的头脑
They say she's hooked on smack but pives preat head.
可能因为她牙齿掉光了吧
Maybe because all her teeth fell out.
安吉利特同时和斯克蕾格之外的好几个姑娘有染
Angelito pimps Scrag and some other girls
但真正龌龊的是罗科 他的狗
but the one who really does the dirty work is Rocco, his dog.
他知道 如果被发现他在威胁一个妓女 他会被抓起来的
He knows he can only be arrested if he's caupht threatening a whore
所以 他尽量不招惹他们
so he manages not to even touch them.
继续，俘获她
Go on, get her.
我和斯克蕾格...感触颇深
Scrag and me... We've got a lot of feeling.
我那样做了 她去拉客
I just do that, and she goes and works the street.
基德...我要给你个礼物
I got a present for you. Kid...
给你的
This is for you.
到底是什么?
What the hell is it?
一套西装
A suit.
你妈妈很快就要被释放了
Your mother's being released soon.
你得穿的体面点
You'll look good in it.
怎么了?
What's up?
你不喜欢吗
Don't you like it?
不是 我只是有点担心
It's not that. It's just I'm a bit scared.
我不知道怎么面对她
I don't know if I can face her.
别这么懦弱 里基
Don't be such a wimp, Ricky.
你得去接她回来
You're going to go and pick your mother up,
还得打扮体面地去
dressed to the nines.
见鬼 这儿有血迹
Shit, there's blood stain on this.
只是一点点
Just a few drops.
嗨 你狠狠揍了一个家伙 然后从他身上扒下这件衣服
Hey, you try beating the shit out of a guy and taking his suit off.
你只管穿上吧
Just try it!
回我家我要给你看样东西
I want to show you something back at my place.
我们都见过你的屁股长什么样
We all know what your asshole looks like.
-拜托  -艾杜 我的茶呢 你像蜗牛一样慢
- Come on.- Edu, my tea. You are as slow as Molasses.
这些都是你卖麻醉品和药丸得来的?
You got all this selling pills and hash?
我攒了五年了
I've been saving for five years.
扯淡
You've got balls.
谁说我和基德不会割断你的喉咙
Who's to say the Kid and I won't slit your throat
然后抢走盒子?
and take the box?
值得思考
A question.
话说回来 你应该对基德再多了解一些
To answer it, you need to know more about the Kid.
两年前 斯克蕾格爱上了一个人
Two years apo, Scrap fell in love with a puy.
他承诺 他不会再让她干这行
He promised he'd take her off the street.
安吉利特和基德去找过他
Angelito and the Kid went looking for him
而且 当然最后找到他了
and, of course, ended up finding him.
告诉我她在哪儿 不然的话我要让你断子绝孙
Tell me where she is or I'll fry your balls.
我不知道
I don't know.
基德 让那狗闭嘴
Kid, will you tell that fucking dog to shut up!
见鬼
Shit!
人们都说基德做事很干脆
People say that the Kid always takes thinps literally
他曾经杀过人
and that he once killed someone.
他们还说 他那天没带枪
They also say he didn't have a pun that day,
他只是把那只狗扔出了窗外
he just threw the dog out the window.
你能不能让那只狗闭嘴
Will you tell that fucking dog to shut up!
妈的
Motherfucker!
我不知道
I don't know.
安吉利特是在说谎
And Angelito is a liar.
我知道 那家伙招了 斯克蕾格又开始拉客
But I know the guy talked, Scrag went back on the street,
一个星期之后 安吉利特又养了条狗
and the next week Angelito appeared with a new dop.
谁说的我和基德不会割断你的喉咙 然后抢走盒子?
Who's to say the Kid and I won't slit your throat and take the box?
滚蛋 你这杂种
Fuck off, you bastard.
滚
Just fuck off.
我们是朋友 你这是干什么
You're a pal. What's this all about?
为我妈妈
It's for my mother.
房屋出租
Building to rent
广岛
The Hiroshima.
我为她开的
I'm opening it for her.
广...什么?
The Hero-what?
看
Look.
我小的时候
When I was little
她总说 她要洗手不干了
she always said she'd quit the street.
她说: "里基 我们要开一家俱乐部"
She said: "Ricky, you and I are going to open a club."
"一个大俱乐部"
"A great club."
她想给它取名叫广岛
She wanted to call it the Hiroshima.
后来她被抓去坐牢 一切都他妈毁了
But she went to jail and everything got fucked.
不 抱歉 里基
No, I'm sorry, Ricky.
她抛弃了你 然后被抓去坐牢
She dumped you and then she went to jail.
你不欠她的
You don't owe her shit.
不过 不管怎样
And, anyway,
你为什么要开一家妓院
why do you want to open a whorehouse?
安吉利特
Angelito,
也许她妈妈喜欢
maybe his mother likes the idea.
是 当然
Yeah, sure.
我妈妈的愿望就是我能为她开一家妓院
My mother's dream is for me to open a whorehouse for her.
这姿势真他么可爱
What a fucking lovely gesture.
那么你不打算加入了?
So you won't come in on it?
那么就帮我找些姑娘来吧
Then help me with the girls.
我知道这是怎么回事
I know where this is going.
你说过 你认识一些人 能从西欧搞到女人
You said you knew people who bring girls from Eastern Europe.
不 我说的是我一个远方表亲的朋友...
No, I said I'd a cousin whose friend...
我知道你说的是谁
I know what you said.
听我说
Listen to me.
我需要三个姑娘 最多四个 仅此而已
I need three girls, four at the most. That's it.
如果你想找一个赚钱的生意 那么
If you want something that's a fucking money-maker, look.
好好算算账吧
Watch-calculators.
这是一桩好生意
It's the new business.
他们又开始流行了
They're in fashion again.
别碰那个
Don't touch that!
如果你不帮我 好吧 为了广岛
If you won't help me, OK, but this is for the Hiroshima.
不 别碰我
No, don't you touch me, OK?
开俱乐部的都是一些真正的杂种
Look, the club business is run by people who are real bastards.
你在听我说吗
You hear me?
街道很龌龊 但那是我们的天下
The street is shit, but it's ours.
-所以 结束了 -不 没有结束
- So it's over. - No, it's not.
我受够了
I've had enough.
我这样做是为了我妈妈
I'm doing this for my mother.
你想让她像我们一样 再次被这行毁了?
You want her to end up on the streets again, like us?
你在哪儿 安吉利特?
Where are you, Angelito?
我们趟这趟浑水
We're both on the fucking street.
安吉利特...
Angelito...
也许我们应该给他找些姑娘
Maybe we could get him some girls,
不行吗?
couldn't we?
闭嘴 你他妈什么都不懂
Shut up, you haven't got a fucking clue.
还有你 里基
And you, Ricky,
别再提起我跟罗马尼亚妓女打交道
don't ever say I traffic with Rumanian pussies,
还是非洲的
or African ones,
还是哪儿的
or with whatever.
基德 你这该死的让我蛋疼
Kid, you are breaking my balls with the goddamned ball.
拜托 走吧
Come on, let's go.
再见 里基
See you, Ricky.
我不喜欢动物
I don't like animals
安吉利特总是把狗往我身上扔
and Angelito always dumps the dog on me.
那是我的 那是我的
It's mine, it's mine!
人们真的都堕落了
And people are really depraved.
今天有个家伙给我100美元 要跟我的狗干
Today a guy offered me 100 to do it with the dog.
狗比我生意还好
The dog pulls in more clients than I do.
踢给我
Kick it to me!
看 那是你爸爸
Look, it's your father.
我的儿子你怎么样了?
How's my crazy boy?
快跑 快跑 快跑
Move, move, move.
-怎么回事 安吉利特? -没什么 很好
- What's up, Angelito? - Nothing, it's all OK.
- 趴下  -放松点儿
- On the ground. - Take it easy.
加油 举起手来
Come on, hands up.
攻击 罗科 上!
Attack, Rocco, attack!
你他妈的 罗科!
For fuck's sake, Rocco!
是警察 不是妓女
The cop, not the whores!
那两个失踪的警察怎么办?
What about the two missing policemen?
失踪了两个?
You've lost two?
就凭你们自己 你们不可能出狱
You guys can't be let out on your own.
祝你好运 基德!
Good for you, Kid!
住手!
Stop!
我抓住他了
I've got him.
港口附近各单位注意
To all units in the vicinity of the port area,
正在追捕一名嫌犯
a suspect is beinp pursued.
- 甜心 - 嗨 爸爸
- Sweety. - Hi, dad.
- 我们又抓住你了 -我想见你 我想念你
- We've caught you again. - I wanted to see you, I miss you.
我也想你
I miss you too,
但我真的很忙
but I've been really busy.
-又是工作... -曼努埃尔!
- With all this work... - Manuel!
- 等等  -好的
- Hang on. - OK.
我们能谈谈吗?
Can we talk?
你知道我为什么要从寄宿学校逃跑吗?
Know why I run away from boarding school?
因为像你 没人愿意跟我这样的人接触
No one touches me like you.
不 我可不愿意摸我自己 那会很尴尬
No, I can't touch myself here, I'd be embarrassed.
求你别那样说话 你让我觉得我很邪恶
Don't say that, please. You're making me feel wicked.
你是在跟你自己说话吗?
Are you talking to yourself?
不 爸爸
No, dad.
别胡闹了
Stop that nonsense.
-见鬼!  -我都没看见
- Shit! - I didn't even see it.
我们得带它去医院
We have to take it to a hospital.
我们哪儿都不去
We're not taking it anywhere.
混蛋 我们不能看着他死
Fuck you, we won't let him die.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
罗科...
Rocco...
看看那些杂种把我的脸弄成什么样了
Look at what those bastards did to my face.
妈的
Fuck them anyway.
他们可以把那俩警察塞到屁股里
They can stick those two cops up their ass.
安吉利特...
Angelito...
真漂亮! 你从哪儿搞到这些轮子?
What a beauty! Where did you get those wheels?
别跟我说你找到了罗科
Don't tell me you found Rocco.
这特么的是什么东西
What the fuck is this?
什么
What?
你从哪儿找到她的
Where did you find her?
站住
Stop!
站住 警察
Stop, police!
站住
Stop!
不许动
Stop moving!
你他妈到底是谁
Who the hell are you?
站住
Stop!
这他妈什么东西
What the hell is this?
这个...
This...
是你妈的复活节彩蛋
It's your fucking Easter egg.
是裸体的女人
A pussy with no papers.
你想加入这桩买卖了 刀都架到脖子上了
You wanted into the business. Now you're up to your neck in it.
-真特么好 -什么?
- Fucking great. - What?
我是这儿唯一有点头脑的人吗?
Am I the only one here who's got any brains?
他们会发现你的俱乐部的
They'll find out about your club.
谁会发现? 警察吗?
Who will? The police?
去他妈的吧
Fuck them.
是的 查理的天使们会来好好侍奉我的
Yeah, and Charlie's Angels can come suck my cock.
我很担心奇诺
I'm worried about Chino.
奇诺?
Chino?
耶稣基督
Jesus Christ.
别告诉我你不知道他是谁?
You don't even know who he is?
不知道
No.
听着 他涉足一切不合法的事情
Look, he's into everything illegal
压榨每一个人
and gets a cut from everyone.
我给你讲个关于他的故事
I'll tell you a story about him
你就明白了
so you can learn.
曾经
Once
一个为他效命的毒枭被捕了
a narco who worked for him was arrested.
奇诺知道 在审判中 那个人会把他拖下水
Chino knew he could testify apainst him in a trial,
他下了血本
and he put so much money on the guy's head
让那个本来要保护那个人的警察 杀了那个人
that the cops who were supposed to protect him, killed him.
听上去不错
So far, so good.
但是被杀的毒枭哥伦比亚的妈妈想要杀她儿子的那个警察的命
But the Colombian's mother wanted the puy who killed him
奇诺不想毁了这桩买卖
and Chino didn't want to lose the coke business,
他抓住他看到的第一个警察
so he took the first cop he saw,
砍下了他的双手
cut off his hands,
砍掉了他的舌头
cut out his tonpue,
把他交给了哥伦比亚家
and handed him over to the Colombian family.
如果被他发现你在单干
If he finds out you're setting up on your own
你就死定了
your life will be shit.
已经如此了 他不能让事情变得更糟
It already is, he can't make it much worse.
把她卖给我
Sell her to me.
3000元 一手交钱一手交货
3,000, right now.
上帝啊 里基 你他妈的真是固执
Jesus, Ricky, you are so fucking hardheaded!
你想独自一人操办起来
You want to set up all on your own,
就为了你那混账妈妈
just for your fucking mother.
他们会抓你的
And they're going to catch you.
我真没用 我帮不了你
And I'll feel like shit because I couldn't help you.
我不会把她卖给你的
I won't sell her to you,
里基
Ricky,
我要租她
I'll rent her.
天哪 我们会被揍得屁滚尿流
Hell, we'll get the shit kicked out of us
惹祸上身的可就不止你一个人了
but you won't be the only one to make a packet.
让我看看那地方
Let's see the place.
真他么脏 里基
It's a fucking dump, Ricky.
你想不想开一家真正的俱乐部
If you want to set up a real club,
说真的 怎么样?
we do it seriously, right?
第一点
First lesson:
不许有二手妓女
No second-hand whores.
广岛将是一个高雅的娱乐场所
The Hiroshima is goinp to be a classy joint.
你会喜欢这个交易的
I've got a deal that you'll like.
我可以捎带着给你提供三个女人
I can offer you three knock-out women.
你可以花2000买下黛西
You can have Desi for 2,000.
她的乳房还很坚挺 它们可是新的
Her tits are still firm, they're new.
蕾蒂1500
Leti for 1,500.
斯克蕾格更便宜
Scrag is even cheaper.
不 不要斯克蕾格
No, not Scrag.
不要斯克蕾格 没门
Not Scrag, no way.
她技术怎么样
How does she suck your dick?
她像个新人一样受用
She leaves your cock as good as new.
-斯克蕾格值200 -算了吧
- Scrag for 200. - Forget it!
100.
买三赠二 像超市里那样
3 for 2, like in the supermarket.
没门儿 白痴
Don't go, dickhead!
婊子养的
Son of a bitch!
你看见我的狗了吗
Have you seen my dog?
我不能卖斯克蕾格 我不能放弃她
I can't sell Scrag, I can't even give her away.
好吧 其他的姑娘怎么样
That's OK, what about the others?
我一直在考虑
I've been thinking about it.
斯克蕾格有点儿讨人厌
Scrag is bit of a nuisance.
要是她能出点小事故就好了
It might be best if she had an accident.
-什么 -怎么了
- What? - What's up?
别打她主意
She isn't going to have an accident.
你是想说 我没胆量那么做?
Are you saying I don't have the balls?
-你是这意思吗? -不是
- Are you saying that? - No.
你就是想说 我没胆量那么做
You're saying I haven't got the balls!
听着 安吉利特
Listen, Angelito...
我没胆吗?
I haven't got the balls?
我不是那意思 我是说 咱们说的可是斯克蕾格
I'm not saying that. I'm saying you're talking about Scrag.
你跟她在一起了多久?
How long are you with her?
可能时间太长了
Maybe too long.
我要挂了 她来了
I'm hanging up, she's here.
车看上去不错
What a great looking car!
你要带我去哪儿?
Where are you taking me?
去乡村 我要给你个惊喜
To the country. I've got a surprise for you.
我也是这么说的
That's what I said.
安吉利特不会把我卖掉的
Angelito wouldn't sell me.
我们惹了太多麻烦 他没那么容易甩掉我
We've been through too much shit for him to get rid of me.
接着 安吉利特
Pick up, Angelito.
当心 亲爱的 别伤到你自己
Careful, love, don't hurt yourself.
闭上眼睛
Don't open your eyes.
也别扭头
And don't turn round.
你会喜欢这个惊喜的
You'll love this surprise.
听着 我有两个选择
Look, I've got two options.
要么我一个人做这些 要花一大笔钱
I do it privately, and pay a fortune,
要么 我依靠国家来完成
or I get it done on the State.
那会是个很漫长的过程
But there's a horribly long waiting list.
我从来没想过这个国家到处都是同性恋
I never knew this country's full of fags.
普利西斯
Princess,
把她带进去
take her inside.
安吉 我以为...
Angel, I thought
你会把我救出这火坑
you were going to take me off the street,
那样我们就...
that you and I...
得了吧
Come on.
忘掉他吧
Forget him.
你值得拥有更多
You're worth a lot.
但是 你知道
But, you know,
你看上去就像一个贩毒的牛仔妹
you look like a Junkie-cow-girl.
好好享受你的生活吧
Make more of yourself.
你吓到我了 你这老杂种
You had me scared, you old bastard.
只要你不伤害她...
If you'd hurt her...
这是什么
What is this?
住手 该死的
Stop that fag stuff.
我们是朋友 不是该死的
We're buddies, but no fag stuff.
-拥抱一下吧 -不
- Give me a hug. - No.
-拥抱一下 安吉利特  -不
- Give me a hug, Angelito. - No.
-一个男人的拥抱  -好吧
- A man's hug. - All right.
别生气了
Don't be angry.
好的 还有一点
All ripht, second lesson.
你弄到钱了 现在去搞些姑娘来吧
You've pot money, now find the pirls.
去哪儿找?
Where?
等着瞧吧
You're about to see.
安吉利特
Angelito,
今天晚上太棒了
it's first class stuff tonight.
对于俱乐部来说 真正的金钱
For the clubs, real money.
周一再来
Come on Monday.
你可以拿到剩下的钱
You can get the leftovers.
你会带你妈妈和你妹妹来吗
Are you bringing your mother and your sister?
看 看
Look, look.
丰乳翘臀 她归我们了
Great tits, a wonderful ass. We'll take her.
多少钱
How much?
-等等 -怎么了
- Wait. - What's up?
看她的胳膊
Look at her arms.
-妈的 是个瘾君子  -是的
- Shit, a junkie. - Yeah.
她妈的
Fuck her.
看左边 看到那个女人了吗
0n the left, see that woman?
那是佛莱达
That's Frida.
她可是色情女王
She's the queen of porn.
她有个姑娘拍黄片
She has a girl fucked in front of a camera,
无论是从前面 还是从后面
from in front, from behind,
不管是跟人还是跟狗 只要有公鸡都可以
with dogs, with Arabs, with anything that's got a dick.
接下来是六号 伊琳娜 斯洛伐克人
We'll continue with number six, Irina. Slovakia.
天然的金发女郎 20000元
Natural blonde. 20,000.
妈的
Shit!
是洛克 你得提防着他
It's Loco. You have to be real careful with him.
谁是洛克
Who's Loco?
谁是洛克?
人人皆知 不是吗
It's obvious, isn't it?
他为奇诺工作
He works for Chino.
如果被他发现了我们在找人 奇诺也就知道了
If he finds out we're looking for material, Chino will find out,
所以要小心点 知道吗
so be careful, OK?
你想要谁就赶紧要
If you want any of them grab them now.
继续 走
Go on, move.
把包给我
Give me the bag.
站她旁边 不许动
Stand here and don't move.
我们走 里基
Let's go, Ricky.
先生们
Gentlemen,
我们赶路 汽车并排停好了
we're in a hurry, the car's double parked.
加油
Come on.
嗨 你在跟踪我吗?
Hey, are you following me?
监视我?
Spying on me?
这是谁?
Who's this?
罗科?
Rocco?
看哪!
Look!
你这死胖子
You big lump!
你还好
You're better!
安吉利特...
Angelito...
怎么回事
What is it?
你看到她看我的眼神了吧
You see how she looks at me?
那个黑女人
The black woman?
感觉就像我们有什么关系 就像...
It's like we're connected, like...
就像有什么替代者
there are "fill-ins".
就像你和斯克蕾格
Like you and Scrag.
替代品?
"Fill-ins"?
我看她像是在往裤子里排大便
I think she looks more like she's shitting in her panties.
你不想入伙吗
Didn't you want to get into the business?
好吧 算你一个
Well, you're in!
说句话
Say a few words.
我说什么
What do I say?
我也不知道 你妈妈是个妓女
I don't know, your mother's a whore.
你毕生精力都投注在了这行 不是吗
You've known the business all your life, right?
接着说 打破这僵局
Go on, break the ice, champ.
你知道你为什么会在这儿
You know why you're here.
这并非易事
This isn't easy.
对谁来说都不容易
Not for anyone.
对你 对我来说 都不容易
Nor for you, not for us.
我不想跟你撒谎
I won't lie to you.
这很难
This is tough.
也很糟
It's shit.
里基...
Ricky...
你吓坏他们了
You're scaring the fuck out of them.
我只是在帮他们
I'm trying to help them.
不 你帮不了他们
No, you can't help them.
他们会把你生吞活剥的
They'll eat you alive.
看看我
Watch me.
好了 这就是广岛俱乐部
All right, this is the Hiroshima Club.
从今以后 你就再也不用离开这儿了 永远不用
From today on, you are not going to leave here, ever.
沉默 敬重一点儿
Silence, a bit of respect
不然的话 我踹你屁股
or I'm gonna have to kick your ass.
她听不懂
She don't understand
你的话
your language.
已经说的很清楚了 听着
It's very clear, look.
我们已经付了一大笔钱
We've paid a shitload of money
在你们身上
for each one of you.
现在 你们欠我们的
And now you are in debt to us.
只有一个办法可以偿还
And there's just one way to pay it.
-不知道什么? -别袖手旁观
- Niet what? - Not do nothing of that.
我们只想离开
What will do is we go.
-你是笨蛋吗?  -你在做什么?
- Are you the smartass? - What are you doing?
-我想揍你丫的 -你个混蛋
- I'm going kick your fucking ass. - You are bastard!
等一下 冷静
Hang on, calm down.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
伊琳娜
Irina.
好的
OK.
你想离开?
You want to go?
那就走吧
Then go.
离开这儿你还能干什么?
What'll you do out there?
找份工作?
Get a job?
你有证件吗?
You got papers?
你有钱吗?
You got money?
离了这儿 你一无所有
You got nothing out there.
你一无所靠
You got nobody.
你想被抓起来送回老家吗?
You want to get caught and sent home?
看着 我们
Here, we are
给你们提供工作
offering you a job.
-体面的工作 -很对
- Decent. - Right.
直到你们还清债务 我们就把证件还给你们
When you pay off your debt we'll give you your papers
那样你们就可以走了
and you can leave.
你做决定
You decide.
你怎么回事?
What's wrong with you?
我们如果不出去赚钱
If we can't go out on the street
我们靠什么来买必需品
how can we buy our things?
给
Here,
玩具钱
toy money.
在这儿你们会得到这些作为报酬
You'll get paid in this.
广岛的专用货币
The only currency in Hiroshima.
如果你们想买东西
If you want to buy anything,
食物 衣服 香烟 我会卖给你们
food, clothes, cigarettes, I'll sell it to you.
当你们离开时 我会把这些兑换成真正的钱
When you leave, we'll swap this for real money.
没有任何欧元交易 明白吗
No dealing in euros. You get that?
欧元?
Euros?
她根本不明白
She has no fucking idea.
嗯 是的 欧元 欧元
Look, yes, euros, euros.
都是合法的
All legal.
都明白了吗
Is that all clear?
欢迎来到广岛
Welcome to the Hiroshima.
你就不能把招牌弄小一点
Couldn't you have got a smaller sign?
而且还是粉色的
And it's pink!
那是我妈妈最喜欢的颜色
That's my mother's favorite color.
但它看上去有点恶心
Yeah, but it looks a bit fudge packer.
在你们开工前 先看一下守则
OK, before we start fucking, let's look at the theory.
基德带来了一些光碟
The Kid's brought a porn movie
所以你们可以从中学习一些姿势和技巧
so you can see all the stuff about postures and things.
振作起来
Let's shape up.
对不起
Excuse me.
枪一直在磨我的公鸡
The gun's rubbing against the tip of my dick
那会让我得湿疹的
it's giving me eczema.
我妈妈明天就出狱了
My mother gets out tomorrow.
我希望她看到这些能大吃一惊
I want her to be knocked out when she sees it.
那是我们才能摘下它来
Then we'll take it down.
我来告诉你我得到了什么
I'll tell you what I've got.
我称之为"狗日的套装"
I call it "the fuck pack".
包括一个避孕套 一包湿巾
It's got one condom, wet wipes,
天蓝色的床单不容易染色
sheets in sky blue, they don't stain so easily.
不过我还是选了浅粉色的
I've got them in pale pink too.
你想不想看看我狗的照片
You want to see a photo of my dog?
罗科和我
Me and Rocco.
那是我
That's me.
看
Look.
喜欢吗
Like it?
想不想碰一下
Want to touch it?
不想?
No?
我可以吗?
Can I?
它抛弃了我
It kicked me.
现在吗?
Now?
-我现在开始吗? -是的 开始吧!
- Will I do it now? - Yeah, do it!
她跑掉了
She's running away!
基德 去抓住她 快抓住
Kid, go fetch! Fecht!
我告诉过你了 那是因为我们太善良了
I told you. This is because we're too nice.
我抓住她了
I got her.
安吉利特! 去你的!
Angelito! Screw you!
进来!
Come in!
好地方!
What a place!
游乐场的灯 弹球机
Its fairground lights, its pinball machine...
它从一个卡车上掉下来 但完好无损
It fell off a truck, but it's perfect.
基德!很好 我想让所有的气球飘起来
Kid! That's good, I want to see all the balloons blown up.
姑娘们 微笑 里基的妈妈要来了
Girls, smile, Ricky's mother is coming.
露出牙齿来
Let me see some teeth.
你!别病恹恹的 我知道你是装出来的
You! Don't get sick, I know you. You're putting it on.
仿皮沙发 看到了吗?
Pleather armchairs, see?
还有 最重要的
And, most important,
消防员的管子 姑娘们就可以揉他们的毛了
a fireman's pole, so the girls can rub their muffs.
斯克蕾格可不擅长做那个
Scrag isn't too good at it.
她正在练习做好
She's practicing.
不过别担心 只要她学会动她的阴部
But don't worry. As long as she can move her pussy
就好多了
we're all right.
微笑 你妈妈出狱那可不是什么天天都有的事儿
And smile, it's not every day your mom gets out of jail.
妈妈...
Mom...
嗨
Hey!
你是谁?
Who do you think you are?
妈妈 是我
Mom, it's me.
里基
Ricky.
你的儿子
Your son.
-我的什么? -你儿子 里基
- My what? - Your son, Ricky.
你说什么
What did you say?
我儿子!
My son!
你想要什么 孩子
What do you want, kid?
听着 5000元你可以为所欲为
Look, it's 5,000 for the whole works.
3500吹箫
3,500 for a blow job.
妈妈 你还好吗
Mom, are you all right?
你感觉还好吗
Do you feel 0K?
天哪 基德 你还认真了
Jesus, kid, you're really going on!
你想让我做你妈妈?
You want me to be your mother?
只要付我钱 我可以做你妈 随便叫什么都可以
Pay me, and you can call me what you want.
-我们得走了 -别碰我
- We have to go. - Don't touch me.
我叫了计程车 在这儿
I called a taxi, it's there.
妈妈
Mom!
起步价50欧元
The minimum fare from here is 50 euros.
没问题
That's no problem.
你现在身上没带钱吧?
You don't take pesetas now, do you?
我一贫如洗
I've got no dough.
我有一个办法
I'll tell you what.
带我离开这儿 我会好好伺候你 我是个妓女
Take me out of here and I'll suck your dick. I'm a whore.
好吧 不是现在 我现在刚解禁回归
Well, not now. I'm being "rehabed" into society.
不过我会吹箫 要收费的
But I'll give you a blowjob, no obligation.
白痴
Shit for brains!
嗨 我宁可跟你走 也不想烂死在这儿
Hey, I'd rather go with you than rot to death here.
先给我50元 别再叫我妈妈
But give me 50 up front and don't call me mom,
不然小心我揍你
or I'll thump you.
同意吗
0K?
见鬼
Shit!
噢 高雅的场所
Wow, classy joint.
安吉利特 他想做
Angelito, he wants to hump.
要我带他上楼吗
Do I take him upstairs?
是的 还在等什么
Yeah, what are you waiting for?
安吉利特 他们在这儿 在停车场
Angelito! They're here! They're parking!
都准备好了 先生们 先生们
Everything's ready. Gentlemen! Gentlemen!
我们开始行动 你们来这儿是为了享受而不是聊天
Let's have some action. You come here to fuck, not to talk.
给你的
It's for you.
给你的见面礼
Your welcome present.
对不起 我想你认错人了
I'm sorry, I think you've got the wrong person.
摘下眼镜来听我说 妈妈
Will you listen and take off those glasses, mom?
别叫我妈妈
Don't call me that.
求你了
Please.
不管你有什么问题 别叫我妈妈
Whatever your problem is, don't call me that.
可以叫我婊子 人渣或者老鸨
Call me bitch and dump the mummy business.
你多大了
How old are you?
23.
我33岁或者34岁 记不清了
I'm 33, or 34, I don't remember.
我怎么可能是你妈妈
How could I be your mother?
基德 基德
Kid! Kid!
当他们进来时 你就松开气球
When they come in, release the balloons.
只要拉一下拉绳就好
Just pull on the string.
我戴眼镜因为我病了
I'm wearing glasses because I'm sick.
狱医告诉我的
The prison doctor told me
就像你脑子里那些乱七八糟的想法一样
I've got that thing you get in your head.
我脑袋里也有一个"垃圾"
A brain "rumor".
等等 脑袋里的"垃圾"
Hang on. A brain "rumor"?
-你是说一个肿瘤?  -不 不是那个
- You mean a tumor? - No, it's not that.
这张纸上写了
It says it on this paper.
是个什么?
A what?
这儿
Here.
茨海默症...
A "tsunami"...
我总健忘 记不住任何事情
I forget things and I can't remember anything.
人们说老人才得这种"塞莱莫"病
They say old people get this "salami" thing,
但是医生说我是由于饮酒过多引起的
but the doctor said it's because I hit the bottle so much.
阿尔茨海默病
Alzheimer's.
她得了老年痴呆症
She's got Alzheimer's.
欢迎光临
Welcome!
妈的!
Fucking hell!
莫碧拉!
Mobila!
快给我找点东西来 她血流不止
Give me something or she'll bleed to death!
给 妈妈 用这个
Here, mom, take this.
真糟糕! 还有 别叫我妈妈
This is shit! And don't call me mom!
这太脏了! 你想让她死于细菌感染吗?
This is filthy! You want her to die of "disinfection"?
找些干净毛巾来
Get clean towels!
加油 莫碧拉
Come on, Mobila.
挺住 加油
Come on, come on!
什么事
Yes?
-推 用力 -普林西斯 我说不出话来
- Push, push! - Princess, I can't talk.
推 用力推 要来了
Push, push! It's coming.
再来些酒...
We need more beer...
妈的 真讨厌
For fuck's sake! That's nasty!
用力 用力
Push, push!
让她从我眼前消失
Get her out of my face.
看着这张脸让我再也不想做爱了
Seen this makes me not ever wanna fuck again.
嗨
Hey,
我说 你永远都不打算出来了吗
listen, are you never going to come?
它来了 用力 要来了 用力
That's it! Push! It's coming! Push!
普林西斯...
Princess...
出来了 就来了
That's it, it's here!
我该怎么说呢 只管干你的
What can I tell you? Cut off your dick!
别说话
And leave us in peace!
它出来了
It's here!
是个男孩
It's a boy.
那到底是什么东西
What the hell was that?
对不起 别伤害我
I'm sorry, don't hurt me.
我不会伤害你
I won't hurt you.
-求求你...  -我不会伤害你的
- Please... - I won't hurt you.
你想揍他 对吗 里基
You want to hit him, Ricky?
对不对
Do you?
你可以放心了
It really relaxes you.
嗨
Hey,
你妈妈状况很不好 她大小便失襟了
your mother's in a bad way. She doesn't remember shit.
安吉利特...
Angelito...
-我做完了 -好的
- I'm finished here. - OK.
我能不能去看看莫碧拉
Can I go and see Mobila?
当然 去吧
Yeah, go on.
-你会让我去吗 -当然 当然会的 去吧
- You'll let me? - Yeah, yeah, go on.
嗨 里基
Hey, Ricky,
那个黑人女孩怎么办
what about the black girl?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
那个孩子 她总不能一边接客一边喂养孩子吧
The baby. She can't fuck and feed it at the same time.
你打算怎么办
What do you want to do?
嗯...
Well...
我不知道
I don't know.
我们可以把那孩子杀了
We could kill the baby.
什么
What?
你怎么可以杀一个婴儿 混蛋
How can you kill a baby, asshole?
把他像个小猫一样 淹死在水桶里
Drown it in a bucket, like kittens.
你脑子有毛病吗
Are you sick in the head?
我不会让你杀任何人
You're not going to kill anybody.
你听见了吗 更别说一个婴儿
You hear? And much less a fucking baby.
-但是... -不行
- But... - No.
-为什么不行 -因为我说不行就不行
- Why not? - Because I say so!
-噢 是吗 -是的
- 0h, yeah? - Yeah.
你太自作聪明了
You think you're so smart.
我总是爱开玩笑
I was joking,
不过现在 我是认真的 我真的要杀掉他
but now I really am going to kill it!
我要抓住他
I'll take that black baby,
在烤箱里烤了 再就着薯条吃了
stick it in the oven and eat it with fries.
你就是个混蛋 里基
You're a piece of shit, Ricky.
我要把这家伙赶走
I'll get this guy out of here.
我们都不想看他死在我们门口
We don't want him dying on our doorstep.
拉格...
Largo...
我是里基
It's Ricky.
我说
Listen.
我记得你提到过一个人
Remember that guy you mentioned who gets children
专门为无法生育的夫妇找孩子
for couples who can't have them.
是的
Yeah.
帮我找找他
Call him for me.
我手头有个孩子
I've got one.
是的 刚出生的
Yeah, just born.
他们要出多少钱
How much do they pay?
出什么事了 里基
What's up, Ricky?
我要把他送走
I'm taking him away.
为什么
Why?
这儿没能力抚养一个孩子
This is no place for a baby.
他不能呆在这儿
He can't stay here.
我要把她送到普利西斯那儿
I'll give him to Princess.
她会照顾他的
She'll take care of him.
他会好好的
He'll be OK.
好的 里基
All right, Ricky.
你决定了吗
Are you sure about this?
把一个婴儿从他母亲身边带走
Taking a child from his mother...
我们只是给他一个家
We're going to give this child a family.
一个真正的家
A real family.
-好吧 -我确定
- All right? - Sure.
我们是在帮他
We're doing him a favor!
-不 里基 -把他带走
- No, Ricky! - Take him.
看看他那可爱的脸 他就像是一个黑黑的小天使
Just look at that darling face. He's like a little black angel.
是的 你真是一个小甜心 对吗?
Yes, you're such a cutie pie, aren't you?
你能照顾好他吗?
Can you look after him?
这孩子不会惹任何麻烦的
This baby will be no trouble.
你是天赐的礼物
You're a gift from God.
我知道那让你很伤心 莫比
I know it hurts, Mobi,
但是 他会过得很好的
but the baby'll be fine.
你真漂亮 你会很出色的
And you're pretty, you'll do OK.
你得去楼下 不然安吉利特要来揪你下去了
You have to go downstairs or Angelito will come and get you!
看这个
Look at this.
这是治疗茨海默症的药 我放这儿了
The pills I've got left for the "tsunami".
这儿没人会花钱为我治病的
No one pays for my treatment out here.
我必须得回到监狱里去
I'll have to go back to jail.
不
No.
别丢下莫碧拉自己 求你
Not leave Mobila alone, please.
我有一个办法
I'll tell you what.
如果你下楼
If you go down,
我就会再多呆几天
I'll stay a few more days.
那些人都是些小丑
Those guys are clowns,
你得坚强 不能让他们看见你哭
but you have to be strong, they can't see you cry.
这样
So,
可以吗
0K?
加油
Come on.
看到了吧 里基
You see, Ricky?
奏效了
It's working.
你妈妈活在自己的世界里
Your mother's in her element.
她看上去对做爱很狂热 但是她就是做老鸨的料
She might be crazy as fuck but she was born to be a "madame".
她怎么还没走
Why hasn't she left yet?
今天早晨 她跟我说她要逃跑
This morning she told me she was broke.
我借给了她100欧元
I lent her 100 euros.
她还要再呆几天 你们可以聊聊天
She's staying for a few days. Maybe you two can have a chat.
我要跟她说些什么呢
What do I say to her?
中国娃娃
China doll!
她看上去那么无辜又让人讨厌
And she looked all innocent and shit.
也许她忘记了她曾抛弃你
Maybe she doesn't remember she dumped you.
也许她不愿意再回想起来
Maybe she doesn't want to remember.
但是你得让她看看 你有种
But you have to show you've got balls
并且敢跟她说 你这婊子
and say to her: "You are a bitch".
然后她就滚蛋了
Then she can fuck off.
至少你把那白痴赶出了你的地盘
But at least you've got that shit out of your system.
昨天是我的生日
It was my birthday yesterday.
38岁了
38,
我都做了些什么
and what have I done?
没拍一部体面的电影
Not one decent movie.
好了
Well,
又有一天 我遇到了一个异装癖
the other day I met a transvestite,
很有明星范儿
star material.
-想来杯啤酒吗  -好的
- Didn't you want a beer? - Yeah.
一个异装癖
A transvestite.
她拥有一切
She's got everything,
而且她掌控着一切
but she's having the operation.
明智的家伙
Wise guy,
你怎么处理那个婴儿了? 把他吃了?
what did you do with the baby? Did you eat it?
什么婴儿?
What baby?
那个黑人女孩生的孩子
The black girl's baby.
什么孩子?
What baby?
-那个黑人孩子 -什么孩子?
- The black baby. - What baby?
那个黑人小孩 你个混蛋
The black baby, you bastard!
-什么孩子 安吉利特? -特么的那孩子!
- What baby, Angelito? - The fucking baby!
你傻吗?
Are you dumb?
普利西斯收养了他
Princess has him.
我跟拉格说了 我们要把他卖给一对很富有的夫妇
I spoke to Largo, we're selling him to a couple with money.
你们这两个聪明的混蛋
You smart bastard.
看得出来
I'll see to it.
那孩子卖了多少钱?
How much for the baby?
25块?
25?
要加30
Ask for 30.
他得到了多少?
How much does he get?
不 直接给了那对夫妇
No, give it directly to the couple,
猜猜他们到底是谁
so find out who the hell they are.
该你走了
Your move.
我在哪儿?
Where am I?
我这是在哪儿?你是谁?
Where am I? Who are you?
我还没做自我介绍
I haven't introduced myself.
人们都叫我奇诺
Everyone calls me Chino.
别听人们诽谤我
Don't believe all you hear about me.
该你走了
Your move.
我怎么会在这儿
I don't know what I'm doing here.
该你走了
Your move.
我想念我的皇后
I'm missing my queen.
在一次游戏中我儿子赢走了它 我让他当战利品保存好
My son won it from me in a game and I insisted he keep it as a trophy.
从此以后 我的棋盘里就少了皇后
Since then, I play without a queen.
我不太懂这个
I don't know much about this.
但是你懂其他一些东西 不是吗
But you know about other things, don't you?
我不明白
I don't understand.
别骗我
Don't lie to me.
现在你就很希望你没走到这儿 对吗
Right now you'd like to be somewhere else, wouldn't you?
可惜 不知不觉的 你的棋子
But, unwittingly, your movements
把你带到了这儿
brought you here.
我没有说谎
I'm not lying.
很好
Very well.
我来给你讲个故事
I'm going to tell you a story,
一个关于族中的故事 而且它能让你明白
a story about respect and about
一个人怎么样对自己的行为负责
how one must accept the consequences of one's actions.
两个月前
Two months ago,
警察拘留了我儿子
the police lifted my son.
无缘无故
For nothing.
他喝醉了跟人打了架
He was drunk and got in a fight.
他才19岁
He was 19.
他们下手太狠了
They hit him too hard.
他当场死了
He died right there.
他们好像很害怕
It seems they got scared
所以
and so
他们毁尸灭迹
they got rid of his body.
你肯定挨不到他们把他藏到哪儿了
You wouldn't know where they hid his body,
你能猜出来吗 里基?
would you, Ricky?
到底怎么回事?
What is this?
你想让我做什么?
What do you want me to do?
现在 你看
Right now, just look.
我抓住了三个警察
I've got three policemen.
实际上 一个已经死了
Actually, one of them died.
他没撑多久
He didn't last long.
但是他帮我找到了另外两个
But first he helped me find the other two.
其中一个敲碎了我儿子的头骨
0ne of these bastards split my son's skull.
另一个袖手旁观
The other just watched.
在你看来
In your opinion,
哪个是罪魁祸首?
which is the guilty one?
这很难说 我知道 因为
It's hard, I know, because
所有的警察都是凶手
all the police look like murderers,
你觉得呢
but what do you think?
站起来
Get up.
站起来 过来 回答我的问题
Get up, come here and answer my question.
别让我过去抓你
Don't make me get you.
怎么样?
Well?
哪个是凶手呢?
Which of them is the murderer?
这个
This one.
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything!
我儿子也是无辜的
Neither did my son.
我只是服从指挥
I just obeyed the commanding officer!
时间一到 我们会把他也处理掉的
We'll take care of him too when the time comes.
不!不!
No! No!
另一个准备
Get the other one ready.
你没服从我的命令
You're working here without my permission.
意味着你一半的所得
That means 50% of the take.
外加没服从命令的罚金
Plus a fine for not respecting your elders.
有话好好说
Let's say
一个星期之内给我100000
100,000 within a week.
怎么样?
0K?
不然的话 我会烧了俱乐部
0r I'll burn the club,
连同你老妈一起烧掉
with your mom inside.
亲爱的妈妈
Dear mother,
我的孩子在九月十号出生
On September 10, my baby was born.
现在他跟我在一起
I have him with me now.
他是个很漂亮的男孩
He is a beautiful boy.
我想现在就回到海边
I would like to go back soon to the sea,
到你身边 这样我的儿子就能看到您 他的奶奶了
to your side, so that my son can know his prandmother.
见鬼
Shit!
你怎么会在我床上
Why are you in my bed?
什么
What?
你想用什么手段上我的床吗
Are you trying to talk your way into my bed?
什么
What?
别妄想了 那小男孩跟我胡扯
Don't try that little boy shit with me.
妈的! 是吗?
Fuck! Yes?
-里基 -在 怎么了?
- Ricky! - Yeah, what?
你他妈在哪儿?
Where the hell were you?
我们倒大霉了
We're in really big shit...
我真受够这地方了 我要走了
I'm sick of this place. I'm leaving.
里基
Ricky!
怎么了
What?
是弗莱达
It's Frida.
如果我们再不给她个姑娘 她就要揍得我们屁滚尿流
She'll beat the shit out of me if we don't give her a girl.
什么?
What?
-我要回监狱去 -你能不能先闭嘴
- I'm going back to jail. - Will you shut up for minute?
他有麻烦了
He's hung up.
我本不想告诉你 但到底是怎么回事
I wasn't going to tell you, but what the hell.
我消失了一段时间 我筋疲力尽了
I've missed a period, I'm knocked up.
上帝啊
Christ!
而且
And
我不会在这儿养孩子 这儿什么都没有
I won't have a child out here where there's nothing,
所以我要回监狱去
so I'm going back to jail.
他们会照顾我
They'll look after me.
你怀孕怎么样了
How are you pregnant?
-普林西斯... -里基
- Princess... - Ricky.
你不会相信的
You won't believe it.
这孩子不愿意用奶瓶 他抓住我的乳头
The baby wouldn't take a bottle, and he grabbed on to my tits,
以你母亲的名义发誓 奶水出来了
I swear on your mother that milk came out.
嗯 也许流出来的那是硅胶
Well, maybe it was silicone,
但是流出了一些东西
but something came out.
安吉利特...
Angelito...
听我说
Listen to me.
你拥有的女孩正是我想要的
You've got a girl that I want.
我明天就想要她
And I want her tomorrow.
否则的话 这小混蛋
0r else this little shit
就死定了
won't have a face.
她是个高个子的黑人女孩
She's a tall black girl.
不 那个女孩不行
No, that girl isn't available.
我们可以给你找别的姑娘
We can give you another girl.
你知道吗 我们导演
You see, the director we work with
看上她了
has taken a fancy to her.
他想让她来演他的新片 我不想让他失望
He wants her for his new movie and I don't want to disappoint him.
里基 你他妈的
Ricky, for fuck's sake,
不就是个妓女吗 给他们
if they want a whore let them have her.
好吧 不过你们得按我说的来
0K, but we'll do it my way.
我可不想那样
That's not what I want.
听着...
Listen...
首先 放了安吉利特
First, let Angelito go.
如果你们守信用 那姑娘明天就归你们了
If you keep your part, you get the girl tomorrow.
不然 买卖就无法成交
If not, there's no deal.
你们必须相信我
So you'll have to trust me.
那个孩子
That kid...
身上有道口子的
He's got a mouth on him.
帕布罗 是维克多 迪亚兹的儿子
"Pablo Diaz, son of Victor Diaz, alias Chino,"
7月23号被捕了
"arrested July 23
因为一次街头斗殴
after a street fight."
他的脑袋受伤了
"He had head injuries."
警官说 他挣扎的时候从楼梯上滚下来了
"The officers said the prisoner struggled and fell down the stairs."
经过审讯 犯人被释放了
"After interrogation, the prisoner was released."
-谁签的审判书? -你知道的
- Who signed the report? - You know.
是的 是你
Yes, you.
你保护你的人 那很对
It's all very well that you protect your people,
但是72小时之内你的所有人马都消失了
but in the last 72 hours your whole team has vanished.
你想让我相信这份审判书?
And you want me to believe this report?
想让我相信 那男孩还活着?
That the boy left here alive?
相信我
Trust me,
不然你就只能单枪匹马了
or you'll be on your own.
看看我给莫碧拉买了什么
Look what I bought for Mobila.
很可爱 不是吗
Lovely, isn't it?
谢谢你 拉菲利多
Thanks, Rafaelito.
里基 我朋友
Ricky, my pal.
狗日的 他们差点杀了我
Fuck you, they nearly killed me!
可你还活着 不是吗
But you're alive, aren't you?
-你伤害了我 -去你的吧
- You hurt me. - You can go fuck yourself.
-向他道歉 -好吧 去他妈的吧
- Apologize to him. - Yeah, and I'll suck his dick too.
自从上次我们做过之后 你还想要
Since you last sucked my dick you want some more.
揍扁这恶心的家伙
Cut out the fag stuff.
拜托 你知道你不会满足的
Come on, you know you can't get enough of it.
这些都是你的
This is all for you.
-我要揍扁你 -随你
- I'll beat the jokes out of you. - For you.
过来
Come here.
六 七...
Six, seven...
9580 就这些了
9,580, that's all there is.
你告诉我 我们怎么向奇诺交待
Tell me how we can pay Chino.
不 你告诉我
No, you tell me.
那个黑人女孩的孩子
The black girl's baby.
你想把他卖了?
Weren't you going to sell it?
是的 30000
Yeah, 30,000.
我们明天能拿到那笔钱
We could bring the swap forward to tomorrow,
但那也不够
but it's not enough.
我可以把莫碧拉的礼物还给她
I could give back Mobila's present.
不 不用担心 基德
No, don't worry, Kid.
你跟他说了那个黑人女孩的事了?
You tell him about the black girl?
什么?
What?
-莫碧拉怎么了? -没什么
- What about Mobila? - Nothing.
没什么
Nothing.
去看看她吧
Go up and see her.
你傻了吗?
Are you fucking stupid?
你要去告诉他关于莫碧拉的事?
Are you going to tell him about Mobila?
我在就想说了 但是我知道你不愿意让说
I won't say I told you so, because you hate that,
但这次我是对的...
but the one time I'm right...
-我早跟你说过了 -是的 你是说了
- I told you so! - Yeah, you did!
我说我要继续干这行
I said to stay on the street
但是你说我们可以出去闯荡
but you decided we could move up in the world.
哦 不
Well, no.
我们得低声下气 任人宰割 你听到了吗
We have to be down below, eating shit, you hear?
他们可不是一般人
They're on a different level.
你知道奇诺付给罗科多少钱吗
You know what Chino pays Loco?
50000 欧元
50,000 euros.
因为他打了人
For slapping somebody around.
有一天 博比告诉我说
The other day, Bobbie told me
这个星期他得到了更多
that this week he'd get thousands more
因为他绑架了一个警察的女儿
for kidnapping a cop's daughter.
什么
What?
一定是奇诺想干那个女孩
Chino must want to fuck the girl.
那个杂种 他很聪明
He's a smart bastard.
他妈的
I'd like to fuck her brains out.
绑架一个警察的女儿  获得更多
A cop's daughter, a different level.
你觉得如果罗科绑架她 他会得到多少钱
How much do you think he'll pay Loco to kidnap her?
为什么 里基?
Why, Ricky?
那女孩还在上学 去查出来
The girl goes to a school, so check it out.
这儿没多少警察的女儿
There can't be many cops' daughters there.
还有一件事
And another thing,
我们要转败为胜
we're going to turn the tables.
他们奈何不了我们 听到了吗
They won't fuck us, you hear?
他们不能把我们怎么样
They won't fuck us.
好吧
All right.
你去找莫碧拉
You take Mobila,
你把她带到佛莱德的店里
you bring her to Frida's store.
看 这都写了
Look, it's all written down here.
计划路线
Calculatinp the route.
-它会指明方向 -是的 它会
- It talks. - Yeah, it talks.
你只管照它说的做
You do whatever it tells you.
之后你用钱将那女人赎回来
Then you pick up the chick with money.
去哪儿
And go where?
去海滩
To the beach.
到海湾去
To the cove.
你把她送到那儿 就可以了
You leave her there. That's it.
有什么问题 给我打电话
If you have a problem, call me.
好的 你要付给我500欧元?
0K, and you're paying me 500 euros for this?
认真的
No messing.
然后我会回监狱里去 你就再也见不到我了
Then I'll go back to jail and you'll never see me again
好的 你明天就开
0K, tomorrow you leave.
你可以回监狱 或者去任何你想去的地方
You can go to jail or wherever you like.
我知道
I know that.
我信守诺言 亲爱的
I know I promised you, love.
维罗妮卡 那不可能 我这周末很忙的
Veronica, it's impossible, I'm tied up all weekend.
我会找个信得着的人去的
I'll send someone I trust.
是的 找个警察
Yes, a policeman.
特么的怎么回事
What the hell is it now?
我想怎么说就怎么说
I'll answer any way I want.
他不生气吗
Doesn't he get worked up?
这和我的胃口
It turns me on.
我喜欢有脾气的人
I like men with a temper.
...你把钱拿走...
...you take the money...
为什么我们女人喜欢的都是些混蛋
Why is it that we women always go for the biggest bastards?
你应该知道的
You should know.
不 你应该知道
No, you should.
安吉利特把你像狗一样对待 甚至不想让你脱离这行
Angelito treats you like shit and won't even let you go out.
我不想说了
I'll shut up.
这是真的
No, it's true.
我不是太明白
I don't get out much.
我要去哪儿
But where would I go?
听着 你带着莫碧拉
Look, you take Mobila.
让她跟弗莱德在一起
Leave her with Frida.
谁是莫碧拉
Who's Mobila?
她在这儿上班 你没见过她吗
She works here. Haven't you seen her?
这孩子是她的
He's hers.
她的
Hers...
如果我们再富有一些 我会用母乳喂养他
If we're gonna get possessive, I'm breast feeding him.
不错
How nice.
你把我带到了一个如此可爱的地方
You've brought me to a lovely spot.
-放松 玛丽莎 -好的 没问题
- Relax, Marisa. - Yes, sure.
你想让他们抢劫我们 再把我强奸了吗
You want them to rob us and rape me?
-玛丽莎... -在我们结婚纪念日
- Marisa... - On our wedding anniversary.
-放松 -不可思议
- Relax. - Fucking unbelievable.
-这是我们的约定 -真好
- This is what we agreed. - Great.
-你把包裹带来了吗 -没 没有包裹
- Have you brought the package? - No, no package.
她得跟我在一起
She has to come with me.
可以 但是...
Yes, but...
里基是那样说的 她来不来 我不管
Ricky said that. She can come or not, I don't care.
亲爱的 跟这位夫人走吧
Darling, go with the lady, please.
相信我
Trust me.
这就是给我的惊喜?
This is my surprise?
真可爱... 别碰我
How lovely... Don't touch me!
如果我能摆脱你...
If I can get away from you...
你会发现 我是这里最有胆的一个
It'll turn out that I'm the only one here with balls.
姑娘们 有火吗
Girls, you got a light?
这些穿露脐装的姑娘们可真无礼
These "Basque" girls are so rude.
你带着孩子
You're to take the baby
到海滩去
and go to the beach.
在那儿你会看到一个女人
You'll meet a woman there.
你知不知道海湾在哪儿
Do you know where the cove is?
那儿
There.
我为什么不能去她家
Why don't I go to her house?
想都别想
Don't you start too.
在海滩上交易是最安全的
It's safest to do the exchange on the beach.
既然你提起来了
Now that you mention it,
我穿的是不是有点正式了
am I bit overdressed?
我有一套假西装 不过为了一个...
I had a camouflage suit too, but an exchange...
我从来没干过的交易
I've never done one.
普林西斯
Princess!
你到底做还是不做
Are you going to do it or not?
你有把握吗
Are you sure about this?
你得为孩子的幸福考虑
You have to think about the baby's happiness.
他们是很有钱 但是他们可是很差劲的父母
They might be rich but maybe they're lousy parents.
起开
Move your ass.
你会达到目的
You are at your destination.
这就是
This is it.
里基跟我说的很清楚
Ricky told me very clearly.
等等
Wait.
这是给你的
This is for you.
给我一个吻
Give me a kiss.
小心
Take care.
我要带着这个
I'll take this,
你们带着这个
and you guys, this.
这是特么什么东西
What the hell is this?
玩具弹丸枪 在两个小时之内我只找到了它
A pellet gun. It's all I could find in two hours.
不过如果你半眯起眼睛看
But if you half close your eyes,
它倒挺逼真的
it looks real.
很好 面罩呢
Great, and the masks?
见鬼
Fucking hell.
我忘记了
I knew I forgot something.
基德 看能不能找到什么我们能用的
Kid, see if you can find anything we could use.
其他的一些东西
Another thing.
我们对一下表  这是给你的
Let's synchronize our watches. This one's for you.
别笑 就这一次 我们得专业点
Don't laugh. For once, we're being professionals.
他妈的
Fuck that.
他们给我500欧元做这些
They're paying me 500 euros for this.
明天我得买把手枪
Tomorrow I'll buy a shotgun,
然后去超市
go to a supermarket,
拿着
hold it up,
好了
and that's it.
在那儿
It's over there.
我可不想坐在这儿整天聊天
I'm not gonna sit here chatting all day long.
你在自讨苦吃
You're a pain in the ass.
就说里基派你来的
Say Ricky sent you!
对不起
Excuse me.
里基让我来的
Ricky sent me.
很好
Great.
这就是我要的那个黑人妓女
This is the black whore I asked for.
给弗莱德打电话
Call Frida.
我一直在想
I've been thinking,
到处绑架人是不对的
and it isn't right to go round kidnapping people.
是的 像你这样的从没绑架过人也是不对的
Yeah, like you've never kidnapped anyone.
那个黑人姑娘
The black girl.
因为我爱她
That was because I love her.
就像你他妈的也喜欢她
Like hell you love her.
你跟他说过那黑人姑娘的事吗
Have you told him about the black girl?
告诉他
Tell him.
我都快要倾家荡产了
I'm going to run out of credit.
嗨  是我
Hi, it's me.
我准备好赎金了
I've got the money for the operation.
我还有些事情要做 然后我得去趟录影棚
I've something to do, then I'll go to the studio.
好的 亲爱的 再见
0K, kisses, ciao.
那个导演...
That director...
总是用做爱来要挟我
Always on about me having a sex change.
我并不是不想做
It's not that I don't want to.
我能怎么办
How can I put it?
电影
Cinema,
你懂的 片子
you know, movies,
会一直存在
will always be there,
在我死后也一样
after I'm dead.
当你大了以后 可以去看
When you're older you can go and see it
可以跟你的朋友们说:"看哪"
and tell your friends: "Look",
"那是我妈妈"
"that one is my mother."
见鬼 真复杂
Shit, it's all so complicated.
好吧
Well,
我得把你放在狗笼子里了
now I have to put you in the dog carrier.
里基说这样比较安全
Ricky says it's safer.
嗨
Hey!
你是来做交易的吗
Are you here for the exchange?
看她 穿着衣服游泳
Look at her, swimming in her clothes.
貌似是伊碧萨
Like it was Ibiza.
那些有钱人都比较怪异
Jet set people are so weird.
你好
Hello.
我给你带来了这个
I brought this for you.
但你得先把钱给我
But first give me the money.
你是个外国人
You're a foreigner.
在我改变主意之前 你最好快点
I'll do this fast before I change my mind.
我想问你个很重要的问题
I want to ask you something important.
每天晚上九点半给那孩子洗澡
Bath the baby every night at 9:30.
一天都不能落
You mustn't miss a day.
还要给他唱歌
And sing to him,
哪怕是用你的方言唱
even in your language.
我经常给他唱摇篮曲
I always sing him to sleep.
好的
Well,
照顾好他
look after him.
妈妈
Ma'am,
好了吗
everything OK?
是的 好了
Yeah, right.
妈妈...
Ma'am...
妈妈 你跑什么
Ma'am, why are you running?
我擦...
For fuck sake...
我妈妈经常那么说
My mother always said that.
"你长着一副多疑的面孔 你会吓到人的"
"You've got a suspicious face, you scare people."
见鬼
Shit.
我们走 他们在这儿
Let's move, they're here.
我要换衣服了 我们得行动了 明白吗
I'll get changed and we'll do something, 0K?
是的 戴上面罩
Right, put on your masks.
这到底是他妈怎么弄的
What the fuck are these meant to be?
嗨 这儿
Hi, there.
还好吗?
Everything OK?
基德 她在那儿
Kid, she's there.
房子真好
What a house.
非常棒 是的 的确如此
Very nice, yes, indeed.
非常好
Very nice.
堵上她的嘴
Cover her mouth!
快点 里基
Come on, Ricky!
罗科 放下枪 放下
Loco, drop the gun! Drop it!
放下枪
Put it down!
跪下
0n your knees.
扔掉那该死的枪 你这杂种
Drop the fucking gun, you bastard!
快点
Come on!
罗科?
Rocco?
是你吗 罗科?
Is that you, Rocco?
罗科是你
You're Rocco.
你在这儿干什么
What the hell are you doing here?
我们又在一起了 事情会好起来的
We're together again, everything'll be fine.
我擦
Come on, for fuck's sake!
捡起来 爸爸 求你
Pick up, dad, please.
没事的 安吉
It's all right, Angel.
没事的
It's all right.
捡起来 求你 捡起来
Pick up, please! Pick up!
挂掉电话
Hang up the phone.
把该死的电话放下
Hang up the fucking phone!
基德 听我说
Kid, listen to me.
我们得走了 警察要来了
We have to leave, the police are coming.
安吉利特死了
Angelito is dead.
不 里基
No, Ricky.
你得帮我
You have to help me.
你得帮我 好吗 头儿
You have to help me. 0K, champ?
什么?
Yeah?
不 罗科不要打电话
No, Loco can't come to the phone.
听着 我得跟奇诺谈谈
Listen, I have to talk to Chino.
说什么?
Yeah?
告诉他我抓住了警察的女儿 他也许会同意的
Tell him I've got the cop's daughter and he might answer!
基德 你要干什么
Kid, what are you doing?
基德
Kid!
基德 你特么到底在做什么
Kid! Where the hell are you going?
基德 擦
Kid, for fuck's sake!
基德
Kid!
我奔着那姑娘来的
I've come for the new girl.
我要带走她
I'm taking her.
我不想伤害任何人
I don't want to hurt anyone.
你好
Hello!
我去见了那个导演
I've come to see the director.
基德 你怎么会在这儿
Kid, why are you here?
嗯...
Well,
来的不是时候 对吗
Bad timing, right?
我还是先走吧
I'd better be going.
告诉那个导演
Tell the director
我筹到钱了
I've got the money for the operation.
拿到东西我就走
I'll pick it up and go.
他给我的这算是什么钱?
What lousy kind of money did she give me?
普利西斯...
Princess...
发生什么事了 吵得我没法拍摄了
What the hell's goinp on? I can't film with this racket/
你干什么去了?
What did you do?
叫救护车来!
Call an ambulance!
莫碧拉?
Mobila?
莫碧拉在哪儿?
Where's Mobila?
你确定你听到了枪响?
Are you sure you heard shots?
-挺住 基德 挺住 -不 他们抓走了莫碧拉
- Come on, Kid, come on! - No, they've taken Mobila.
她不在这儿
She isn't here.
妈的
For fuck's sake!
快走 我们走
Come on, let's go.
他们不会骗我们的
They're not going to screw us.
他们不会 你还跟着我吗
They're not. Are you with me?
-是的 里基 -他们抓不到我们
- Yes, Ricky. - They won't catch us.
是血
This is blood.
里基 我要死了
Ricky, I'm dying.
不 你不会死的
No, you're not dying.
我要死了
I'm going to die.
你不会死的
You're not going to die.
好了 好了 按这儿 基德
All right, all right, press here, Kid.
用力
Hard.
我去找医生来
I'll call a doctor.
你会没事的
You're going to be fine.
没事的 里基
It's all right, Ricky.
不会有事的
It's all right.
听着 基德
Listen, Kid.
奇诺要来了
Chino is coming.
他会为了那个女孩儿给我们一大笔钱
He'll give us a shit load of money for that girl.
我们拿到钱 就离开这儿
When we have the money we'll get out of here.
走的远远的
Go far away.
是我 普林西斯
It's me, Princess.
你好 普利西斯
Hi, Princess.
我来完成我的交易
I'm having my operation.
初生牛犊不怕虎
Begginers luck.
请稍等
Just a minute, please.
他们要把我干掉 我却在这儿闲聊
They're poing to knock me out and I'm here chatting away.
我很高兴你跟我来
I'd like you to come,
那样我就不再孤单单一个人了
so I'm not alone.
我知道这看上去就像是剪切和粘贴
I know this is just like cut and paste,
不过我还是有点害怕
but I'm still kind of scared.
求你 让我回家吧
Please, let me go home.
别伤害我 我想回家
Don't hurt me, let me go home.
放松一点 亲爱的
Laugh a little bit, honey.
生活已经够惨了 别像世界末日来临似的哭丧个脸
Life's sad enough without you looking like a wreck.
我爸爸是警察
My father's a policeman.
警察?
A policeman?
那太好了
That's perfect for me.
继续
Go on.
拿着这玩意儿
Take this gadget
给你爸爸打电话
and call your father.
拨号码
Dial the numbers.
爸爸 我是维罗妮卡
Dad, it's Veronica!
我是维罗妮卡 爸爸
It's Veronica! Dad!
别挂电话
Hang on.
听着 我们绑架了你女儿
Listen, we "did a kidnap" on your daughter.
至少得判我20年
I should get at least 20 years.
蹲大狱
In jail.
什么?
What?
他说我是白痴
He says I'm nuts.
要想见到她你得来这儿
If you want to see her, you have to come here.
不 警察先生 什么都不要
No police, nothing.
你得来逮捕我
You have to arrest me.
别挂电话 我告你地址
Hold the line a minute, I'll give you the address.
等等
Wait.
亲爱的 你知道这是哪儿吗
Hon, you know where this place is?
让我歇一会儿
Give me a fucking break.
绷带在哪儿
Where are the bandages?
就放在这儿的 它们去哪儿了
They were here. Where are they?
你总是把我的东西到处乱扔
You're always moving my shit around.
我的绷带包就放在这儿的 它去哪儿了
I had my bag of bandages here. Where is it?
放哪儿了
Where is it?
我要走了
I'm leaving.
你哪儿都不去 看着我
You're not going anywhere. Look at me.
你哪儿都不去
You're not going anywhere.
你那英雄之举可骗不了我
You don't fool me with your tough guy act.
谢谢上帝 你不是安吉利特
Thank God, you're not Angelito.
我以为你所需要的就是爱情
I think that what you need is affection.
但是你得为此努力
But you have to work at it.
当你失败两次以后 很容易放弃
It's easy to give up when you've been knocked down twice.
我跟你这么说
I'm telling you this
是因为我也如此
because I'm like you.
我随波逐流
I go along with people
但我并不觉得这有多糟糕
and I don't see that they're screwing up my life.
生命短暂 里基 转瞬即逝
And life's too short, Ricky. It's too short.
斯克蕾格...
Scrag...
我不叫斯克蕾格
My name isn't Scrag.
我叫苏蕾达
It's Soledad.
100000 是吗
100,000, right?
那个女孩 求你
The girl, please.
你让我大吃一惊
You surprised me.
你期待着敌人出手
You anticipated your opponent's move.
你很需要这笔钱 拿去吧
You deserve this money. Take it.
好多血
A lot of blood.
你不得不牺牲一个小卒吗
Did you have to sacrifice a pawn?
在楼上
Up the stairs.
走廊尽头
At the end of the corridor.
等等
Wait.
你要干什么
What are you going to do?
你知道的
You know.
你想阻止我吗
Are you going to try to stop me?
你不会做任何事 你知道为什么吗
You won't do anything. You know why?
你拿了钱
You've taken the money.
我们现在是拴在一条绳上的蚂蚱
Now we're both on the same side.
快点 我们得走了
Come on, we have to go.
我们都得走了
We both have to go,
一起走
together.
好不好
0K?
我们能去哪儿
Where could we go?
你说呢
You go on.
如果警察来了 就一团糟了
If the police come it's gonna be a mess.
我要去厕所
I'm going to the toilet.
-孕妇尿频 -你不是孕妇
- Pregnant women piss all day. - You're not pregnant.
你怎么知道的
How do you know?
我怀孕的时候就那样
I was pregnant once and it was just like this.
-你怀过孕? -是的
- You were pregnant? - Yes.
后来呢?
And what happened?
很糟糕
Awful.
牧师让我堕胎了
The priests made me abort.
很好
Just as well.
你想想 让一个孩子跟做妓女的妈妈整天呆在窑子里
Imagine a child on the street all day with a whore for a mother.
那将是个噩梦
That scars you forever.
对那个孩子来说
The best thing for that child
不要出生就是最好的
was not to be born.
妈妈 看着我
Mom, look at me.
看着我
Look at me.
我是里基
I'm Ricky.
里基 你的孩子
Ricky, your child.
你儿子
Your son.
妈妈 我是里基 你的孩子
Mom, I'm Ricky, your child.
真的吗 对不起
Really, I'm so sorry.
我想不起来了
I can't remember.
你抛弃了我
You abandoned me.
我12岁的时候 你把我扔在街头
You dumped me on the street when I was 12.
也许你不想记起来 但是你生下了我
Maybe your head doesn't want to remember, but you fucked me up.
我相信你还记得
I think you do remember.
那是什么
What's that?
是我
That's me.
那是我
And that's me.
你可骗不了我 你在说谎
You can't fool me. You're lying.
-那是我 -你在说谎
- That's me. - You're lying to me.
那就是我 妈妈
That's me, mom.
那不可能
It's not true.
你到底在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
你为什么要撕了那照片
Why are you tearing up the photo?
-妈妈...  -别叫我妈妈
- Mom... - Don't call me mom!
我不是你妈妈
I'm not your mother!
我要去厕所 我回来时可不想再见到你
I'm going to pee. When I come back I don't want to see you here.
我叫了警察来把我带回监狱 那才是属于我的地方
I've called the police to take me to jail. That's where I should be.
-你... -放松
- You... - Take it easy.
我女儿在哪儿
Where's my daughter?
快告诉我
Tell me now.
不许动 听到没有
Don't move! You hear me?
嗨 你!
Hey, you!
我女儿在哪儿
Where's my daughter?
她在哪儿 婊子
Where is she, bitch?
我女儿在哪儿
Where's my daughter?
快告诉我 她在哪儿
Will you tell me now? Where is she?
在楼上?
Upstairs?
爸爸...
Dad...
桑托斯
Santos,
我知道 你一定不想错过这个
I knew you wouldn't want to miss this.
放开她
Let her go.
你要杀了我吗
You going to shoot me?
好啊 开枪吧
Go on, try it.
开枪
Shoot.
放开她
Let her go.
如果你走运
If you're very lucky,
也许你会打中我
you might hit me.
我不会失手的
But I won't miss.
开枪
Fire.
你不开枪?
You won't fire?
那就放下你的枪
Then drop your gun.
扔掉
Drop it.
别担心 亲爱的
Don't worry, love.
我让你放下枪
I told you to drop your gun.
你们严刑逼供 最后杀了我儿子
You tortured and killed my son.
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything.
我发誓
I swear.
你对他的尸体做了什么
What did you do with his body?
有种就告诉我你对他的尸体做了什么
At least have the decency to tell me what you did with his body.
还是你觉得在你女儿面前羞于启齿
0r are you ashamed to tell me in front of your daughter?
她还是个孩子
She's a child.
她没有错
She's not to blame.
孩子是无辜的
Children are innocent.
她不该替她的父亲承担罪孽
They shouldn't pay for their fathers' sins.
那不公平
It's not fair.
谁说的这个世界就得公平
But who said the world was fair?
现在她听不到你说话了
She can't hear you now.
说吧
Talk.
我们不知道那是你儿子
We didn't know it was your son.
他们叫我过去 我看到了他
When they called me and I got there and saw him,
他已经死了
he was already dead.
我得保护人民
I had to protect my people.
我们把他的尸体运出海
We took his body out to sea
沉到了海里
and sank it.
现在我要让你看看我怎样折磨死你女儿
Now you'll see how I torture and kill your daughter.
别那样 你很幸运
Don't look like that. You're lucky.
看到我儿子还活着的愿望 一点一点的在折磨着我
The hope of seeing my son alive again destroyed me bit by bit.
我会让你死得痛快的
I'll destroy you in one go.
你想干什么
What are you going to do?
告诉我
Tell me.
你想怎么样
What are you going to do?
什么?
What?
别害怕 亲爱的
Don't worry, my love.
他们说
They say
人死前的一霎那
that a split second before you die
你的一生会在眼前一一闪过
your whole life passes before your eyes.
那是骗人的
It's all a lie.
你只能想到一件事
You can only think of one thing.
你会想
You think
活着的人多幸运啊
how lucky the living are,
那些人还能呼吸
the ones still breathinp.
醒醒
I want you awake.
睁开眼睛
Don't close your eyes.
Keep your eyes open!
你能想起一些事情吗
You know something?
也许我还不想回监狱里去
Maybe I won't go back to jail yet.
事实上 那儿的伙食很烂
The truth is, the food's crap.
我们的境况不是太糟
And things haven't gone so badly for us.
妈妈...
Mom...
什么?
What?